mardox.com 2016-10-26

# Mardox.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices on the Mardox Corp website at Mardox.com. Mardox Corp., is committed to providing our visitors with a website that respects their privacy. We do automatically gather personal information from you, such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address. This information is only obtained if you supply it voluntarily, usually through contacting us by e-mail or registering in a portion of the Mardox site. 

## Personal Information Management 

When you visit Mardox.com, our web servers automatically collects a limited amount of standard information essential to the operation and evaluation of the web site. This information includes: 

the date and time of your page request   
the IP address your computer is using to receive information   
the type and version of your browser   
the page from which you arrived at our site

This information helps us assess our information services and is used only for this purpose. This information is not used to identify individuals who come to the web site. 

If you choose to provide your personal information in an e-mail to someone else, or by filling out a form with your personal information included and submitting it through our website, Mardox Corp, will use that information to respond to your message and to help provide you with the information you have requested.

The personal information you submit is secure once it reaches our servers. In transit between your computer and the server, however, it may not be secure.

## Cookies and Session Variables

This website uses cookies and session variables. Cookies are small amounts of information that are distributed to web browsers to assist you when you return to the site or a specific area on the site. The cookie used here retains session information, or more specifically, the options selected to determine your itinerary or to keep track of the items you wish to purchase (session cookies remain active only until you close your browser). Mardox Corp, does not keep a database of information obtained from these cookies or session variables.   

## Online Transactions 

All payment related transactions are conducted through PayPal.com.

When you ask to purchase a product or membership from this site, you will have to submit personal identifying information, such as your name, the name of your company or organization (where applicable), your shipping and billing address(es), your phone and fax numbers, your e-mail address, the item(s) you have purchased. Your credit card number and expiry date will never be required on the Mardox.com web site. All payment information such as credit card info will be processed through PayPal.com. 

When you submit this information, it is stored in a secure server. The information collected is used to process and deliver your order or membership, as well as inform your Affiliate Manager of your order. This information is not disclosed to any Third Party except to authorized employees of Mardox Corp, who need it to process your order and bill or as required by law. The contact information you provide may also be used to contact you in the future about your order or membership.

## Internet Connection Security

All personal information that you provide during your on-line payment transaction (including your credit card information) is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Encryption. When your information is encrypted, it is scrambled and rendered unreadable to anyone else. This type of transaction is conducted through the PayPal.com servers.  

## Security

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Mardox Corp employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, or investigation of malicious attacks on our servers, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.   

## Links to Other Sites 

This website contains links to external sites. Mardox Corp is not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other websites, and we encourage you to examine each site�s privacy policy and disclaimers in order to make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found therein.  

## Retention of Your Information 

Only information necessary for the operation of the website and the provision of requested materials or services to you is collected. The information is used only for the purpose it was collected or for a consistent purpose. For instance, you may be contacted regarding the Mardox Corp website, specific areas of the website, or services purchased on the site for quality, improvement or evaluation purposes. The information is only retained for the length of time necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected.   

## Contact Information 

For more information about the collection of your personal information, any of the policies described above or about our website in general, please Click here to contact us.
